<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>n0pe.org</title>
    <description>The Home of Arthur Reeder
</description>
    <link>/</link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 03:08:24 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 03:08:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Broke my Site</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I feel rather dumb. When the Jekyll 3.0 update on Github happened, Like a long time ago, it somehow broke my theme. I couldn’t update.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The worst part about it is the fact that I had no idea it was broken.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;derp&quot;&gt;DERP&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been developing a new custom Jekyll theme that I will both be publishing as an open source project and as my new website theme. It’s not ready. So until then I’ll be rocking the default.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Now back to our regularly scheduled blogspam.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>/2016/02/22/broke-my-site/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2016/02/22/broke-my-site/</guid>
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Maggical Friggin&#39; Ponies</title>
        <description>&lt;div style=&quot;margin: 0 auto; width: 640px;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;video width=&quot;640&quot; hight=&quot;360&quot; src=&quot;https://archive.org/download/magical-friggin-ponies/magical-friggin-ponies.webm&quot; controls=&quot;&quot;&gt;


You can grab ponysay at [https://github.com/erkin/ponysay](https://github.com/erkin/ponysay)

The hak5 video in question: [https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mbrXsL8TUrU](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mbrXsL8TUrU)

Sorry about the audio. Still working out the bugs.
&lt;/video&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2016 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>/2016/02/18/magical-friggin-ponies/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2016/02/18/magical-friggin-ponies/</guid>
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Going to Scale 14x</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This will be my first year attending the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.socallinuxexpo.org/scale/14x&quot;&gt;Southern California Linux Expo&lt;/a&gt;. I’ll only be there Sunday and I only could afford a general admission ticket but I’m sure it’ll be very fun. Plus, it’s in &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pasadena,_California&quot;&gt;Pasadena&lt;/a&gt; which is nice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My cohort Johnstar and myself will be running around the Pasadena Convention Center until we are overcome with hunger. At that point we might partake in some local LA burgers. (Probably In-N-Out, almost always is)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m very excited and I hope to meet some fellow nerds. If you’ll be there on Sunday and you wanna say “yo”, hit me up on Twitter &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/arthursucks&quot;&gt;@arthursucks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2016 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>/2016/01/13/scale41x/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2016/01/13/scale41x/</guid>
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fight the Writing Funk</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I find it hard to write. I should be writing a lot more. Everyone should. It clears the mind and some have claimed it does more than yoga or &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/better-humans/better-than-meditation-12532d29f6cd#.lf37b4t5g&quot;&gt;meditation&lt;/a&gt;. So why is it so damn hard to take 30 minutes to do some basic writing? Just like working out, once you get started you’ll feel more into it. I workout 3-5 times a week depending on my schedule. I should also be writing. (Too bad I can’t write while working out.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I keep a simple word processor on all my devices. Got one on my computer, laptop, tablet, and even my phone. Any time I got an idea while I’m on the bus or wherever I just let it flow out. Recently it’s not been finding it’s way onto this blog but the creative juices are definitely flowing more often. Even this post is much easier for me to pour out because of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are a few things I should be doing that I don’t do:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I don’t schedule time in my week for writing.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I don’t read enough. (I only read two books in all of 2014)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I have a brand new (2010) AP Style Guide that I haven’t picked since I got it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The rule I need to remember, just like anything else in the creative world. A terrible completed piece is better than a incomplete masterpiece. Write as much as you can. Practice make perfect as they say. Keep writing.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2015 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>/2015/12/01/fight-the-writing-funk/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2015/12/01/fight-the-writing-funk/</guid>
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Comments</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Let’s talk about comments. Well, actually, you’re only going to &lt;strong&gt;read&lt;/strong&gt; about comments because I’ve decided to remove the comment function from this site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few months ago a site I read regularly, &lt;a href=&quot;http://theverge.com&quot;&gt;The Verge&lt;/a&gt;, turned off their comment system supposedly because of overly offensive and hostile comments. Personally I think this is a bullshit. Ultimately it’s their site so their rules.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When &lt;a href=&quot;http://vice.com&quot;&gt;Vice.com&lt;/a&gt; removed the comments from their blog they admitted to doing a poor job moderating the comments section. That reason hit home. Strike one, &lt;strong&gt;I’m lazy&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So let’s take laziness and add the concern of privacy. Part of the reason I originally wanted to run WordPress is because I care about privacy. Not just my privacy but the privacy of my readers. Yes. I care about you. I recently added &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Transport_Layer_Security&quot;&gt;TLS&lt;/a&gt; to my site as a light layer of protection. I switched to Jekyll for a variety of reasons but one of those reasons was having full control of how my site was built.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;i-guess-ill-get-to-the-point&quot;&gt;I guess I’ll get to the point.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In attempt to keep discussions where they belong and to maximize the options of privacy the comments will be missing from this site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have been thinking about making a page on either &lt;a href=&quot;https://voat.co&quot;&gt;Voat&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://reddit.com&quot;&gt;Reddit&lt;/a&gt; in the future. Though most of my pages usually don’t get enough comments to justify that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can, however, get a hold of me on &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/arthursucks&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>/2015/10/23/comments/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2015/10/23/comments/</guid>
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Joy of Jekyll</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/jekyll.png&quot; alt=&quot;Jekyll&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like many before me, I’ve ditched Wordpress and took the plunge into Jekyll. It was natural to use Jekyll after working with WordPress for so long. There are trade offs but I feel that Jekyll is a better platform for my creativity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the last year or so I’ve really thrown myself into using VIM. It’s availble on my Apple PC at work, my Chromebook (With Crouton) and ofcourse my Linux box at home. (For Android I like &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/vmihalachi/turbo-editor&quot;&gt;Turbo Editor&lt;/a&gt;.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VIM and Jekyll go great together&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;hosting&quot;&gt;Hosting&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To host a plain text website there are a million choices. My two favorites at this moment are &lt;a href=&quot;http://surge.sh&quot;&gt;Surge.sh&lt;/a&gt; and the very popular &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com&quot;&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt;. I ultimately went with Github because I can make updates with git. I like git.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;cloudflare&quot;&gt;Cloudflare&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cloudflare.com/&quot;&gt;Cloudflare&lt;/a&gt; is a popular (and sometimes &lt;a href=&quot;https://scotthelme.co.uk/tls-conundrum-and-leaving-cloudflare/&quot;&gt;controversial&lt;/a&gt;) service. They act as a free CDN but also offer a lot of other awesome features. I use them for the free TLS. This adds a layer of encryption between the user and the domain but doesn’t encrypt between the domain and the server. After thinking it through, I decided that a little security is better than zero security. Hopefully once the &lt;a href=&quot;https://letsencrypt.org/&quot;&gt;Let’s Encrypt&lt;/a&gt; project takes over I can add full encryption from Github.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most my dynamic sites will probably go this route with the exception of &lt;a href=&quot;http://consbeeracy.com&quot;&gt;ConsBEERacy&lt;/a&gt;. ConsBEERacy is a podcast that I work on (I’m not one of the hosts, sorry. The hosts are really awesome and you should listen!) and it needs the WordPress framework.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2015 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>/2015/10/01/joy-jekyll/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2015/10/01/joy-jekyll/</guid>
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
        <category>commandline</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dennis Ritchie: Unix Thug</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;alignright&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; src=&quot;/images/dennis-ritchie-tuac.jpg&quot; /&gt;Life’s not easy for a thug. He lived hard, and was taken from us at the young age of 70.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dennis MacAlistair Ritchie was an OG American computer scientist. Not only did he create the C programing language but he also co-authored Unix OS with his homeboy, Ken Thompson.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;lt;/br /&amp;gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;aligncenter&quot; src=&quot;/images/pouritour.gif&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2015 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>/2015/09/09/dennis-ritchie-unix-thug/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2015/09/09/dennis-ritchie-unix-thug/</guid>
        
        <category>Funny</category>
        
        <category>News</category>
        
        <category>Unix</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Artwork in Long Beach</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/longbeachart.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m really lucky to live a very artistic and creative community. I spent about 20 minutes downtown looking around at some of the awesome artwork that is displayed around my city.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-3&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/images/IMG_20150829_105527.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/th/IMG_20150829_105527.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-3&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/images/IMG_20150829_110405.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/th/IMG_20150829_110405.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-3&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/images/IMG_20150829_110514.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/th/IMG_20150829_110514.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-3&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/images/IMG_20150829_110639.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/th/IMG_20150829_110639.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-6&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/images/IMG_20150829_114755.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/th/IMG_20150829_114755.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-6&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2015 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>/2015/08/29/artwork-in-long-beach/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2015/08/29/artwork-in-long-beach/</guid>
        
        <category>artwork</category>
        
        <category>lbc</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NoodleBox: My new battle station</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/hp-stream-200-010.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;HP Stream 200&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/images/amd-6300.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;alignright&quot; src=&quot;/images/th/amd-6300.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Computers have traditionally been gigantic boxes that bellow out heat, take up valuable desk space, and somehow both collect and expel dust. My AMD 6300 Quadcore Bulldozer powered battle station was the ideal balance between muscle and cost effective PC building. 90% of the processing power that Intel sold at a fraction of the price. At least that’s how it was four years ago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was unfortunate enough to have my trusty AMD die off after years of service. When I say die, I want you to keep in mind that most of the components where still very functional. The power supply and the motherboard simply engaged in an apparent suicide pact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The hard drives are sitting on my desk awaiting USB3 enclosures The RAM and chip have been donated to a friend. Some of you might be wondering why I didn’t simply buy a new parts and rebuild. It simply comes down to cost and need.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve purchased the new HP Stream 200 with an Intel Celeron 2957U. This chip doesn’t have the muscle that the AMD had in terms of raw computing power. However, other than video editing and rendering is that even noticeable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Idealy I’d like to do a full review of the hardware but there isn’t much I can bring to the table that hasen’t been &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://youtu.be/Ro4VWSBPJ00&quot;&gt;covered in this video&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2015 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>/2015/08/27/noodlebox-my-new-battle-station/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2015/08/27/noodlebox-my-new-battle-station/</guid>
        
        <category>linux</category>
        
        <category>hardware</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Remember that time I was caught on Google Maps?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;So I guess the street view car grabbed a shot of me when I was heading out to the local liquor store for another 80oz bucket of fizzy caffeine. I saw the car go by but I’ve seen the street view car several times. This time I actually ended up &lt;a href=&quot;https://encrypted.google.com/maps/@33.783028,-118.132319,3a,75y,5.39h,66.81t/data=!3m6!1e1!3m4!1slv3OU5FMHMmM0K4a6np3pg!2e0!7i13312!8i6656&quot;&gt;online&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/doing-my-thang.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I haven’t learned my lesion either. I still venture out to the sunlight for a tasty beverage several times a day.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2015 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>/2015/06/19/remember-that-time-i-was-caught-on-google-maps/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2015/06/19/remember-that-time-i-was-caught-on-google-maps/</guid>
        
        <category>Funny</category>
        
        <category>News</category>
        
        <category>Google</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
